Welcome to my channel.
Today I will show you how to make a
double-sided sewing machine.
First, I will show you how to make a
We can choose the sewing tool
and sew the pieces together.
The difference between a double-sided sewing machine
and a double-sided sewing machine is
that the double-sided sewing machine
can only be used in a 3D window.
Select the double-sided sewing machine
and click 10 points.
Click the end of the creation.
Create the first set of double-sided sewing machines.
Then use the same method to create the other side.
After we hide the sewing machine,
we can notice the difference
between a double-sided sewing machine
and a double-sided sewing machine.
The part where the double-sided sewing machine
is used has a line gap
and can't set the folding angle
and the type of sewing machine.
After displaying the sewing machine,
use the double-sided sewing machine
to set the length of the line.
We can set the length of the line
in the property editor.
In order to prevent the sheet from falling,
I can press W first
and click the sheet.
Add a fixed needle
and fix the sheet in the 3D window.
After setting the length of the line,
you can notice that the middle part
is opened.
If you continue to increase the length of the line,
the gap in the middle will be larger.
Press W on the wrong side.
If you make a cuts using the double-sided sewing machine,
you can easily adjust the length
of the line.
Here you are.
After adjusting the length,
the lines will be re-selected.
Press W with the double-sided sewing machine
to set the length.
Press W to adjust the length
and press W to adjust the length.
After you adjust the length,
The line is reset and the two sides
are connected to each other.
Please note that the direction of the sewing needle should be the same as the direction of the sewing needle.
If the direction of the sewing needle is different, there will be an unstable situation when the sewing thread is crossed and simulated.
Of course, when sewing, you can also sew one short side and one long side at the same time.
You can also use a cut-off seam in the inside of the board.
If the direction of the sewing needle is different, there will be an unstable situation when the sewing thread is crossed and simulated.
If the pants fall down easily, we can use a virtual model line seam to sew the clothes and fix the clothes on the model.
Thank you for watching. Please subscribe to our channel.
Select the virtual model line seam later.
Add a round seam along the pants
Press Ctrl at the time of addition to add a mixing point
Add a vector line
No.2 widest punt
No.3
After the design is completed after simulation, the pants will be placed in the place where the line seam of creation is created.
Click on the sewing line and set the length of the sewing line for it, and when there is a certain gap between the model and the clothing, it will be more stable.
Next is another small case, you can notice that the belt on the pants will slide down, even after increasing the friction, it will slide down.
We can use the clip-on tool, click on the belt and the pants, and fix them.
Next, we can use the clip-on tool, click on the belt and pants, and fix them.
Sew the left and right sides of the strap.
If we simulate it directly, the small strap will fall down because it is not fixed.
So we can use the fake sewing tool to fix the small strap on the big strap.
We can notice that there is a larger gap between each layer of the strap, so we can reduce the impact thickness of the strap and reduce the gap.
But if we simulate it directly, it may cause the simulation to be unstable due to the one-time reduction of the impact thickness.
Therefore, we can stabilize the simulation layer by layer, and then simulate the outer layer of the strap.
In this example, there is a large gap between each layer of the strap and the outer layer of the strap.
So, we can see that there is a large gap between each layer of the strap and the outer layer of the strap.
And then we can simulate the simulation layer from here.
And we can see that the small strap on the other side is in the middle of the snap.
You can also adjust the length of the line to control the position of the small tie after selecting the
length of the line.
You can also adjust the length of the line to control the position of the small tie after
selecting the length of the line after selecting the length of the line after selecting the